arduino-info.wikispaces.com 2015-11-28

# Wikispaces by TES - Privacy

Last Updated 17 November 2014 (General refresh and safe harbor details)

We don't spam, we don't sell your personal information, and you can opt-out of all emails sent by our site.

We don't give out your name or email address. Period.

You're in complete control of what people find out about you on Wikispaces. We do not show your name or email address to anyone through the site or through any other mechanism.

The rest of this notice describes our privacy policy, or privacy notice. By visiting Wikispaces.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. This privacy notice applies to wikispaces.com which is owned and operated by Tangient LLC. This privacy notice describes how Tangient LLC (collectively referred to here as "We", "Us", "Our") collects and uses the personally identifiable information you provide on our website wikispaces.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personally identifiable information and how you can access and update this information.

Tangient LLC has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy notice and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal. The TRUSTe certification covers only our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through wikispaces.com and our service Wikispaces. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which you have engaged Tangient LLC.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concerns that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact us. You may also [contact TRUSTe](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

Tangient LLC complies with the U.S. - E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Tangient LLC has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Tangient LLC’s certification, please visit 

<http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

## Registration

In order to use this website, you must first complete the registration form. During registration you are required to provide us your username and email address. We use this information to contact you about the services on our site.

Tangient LLC is the sole owner of the registration information collected on Wikispaces.com.

## Orders

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

## Uses of Information

Wikispaces.com uses your personally identifiable information to contact you about the site. We do not disclose your name or email address to other users of Wikispaces.com.

## Updates

We will occasionally send you information about our website and services. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the "Choice / Opt-out" section of this document.

## Service-Related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

## Customer Service

Based upon the information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email.

## Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We may collect aggregate information about our user base. For example, we may keep track of the number of users that have registered or the number of wikis that have been created on wikispaces.com. We may display this information publicly or provide it to others.

## Personally Identifiable Information

We do not share personally identifiable information with third parties. We do not share your email address with third parties.

## Agents

We may use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

## Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product or service but do not wish to receive any additional communication from us, you can indicate your preference on your Settings Page.

If you no longer wish to receive our promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or as described on your Settings Page.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

Technologies such as cookies, beacons and scripts are used by Tangient LLC and our analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the website, tracking user movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual or an aggregated basis.

We use cookies to remember user settings (e.g. language preference) and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited.

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) using HTML5 or Flash to store preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site use LSOs using as HTML 5 or Flash to collect and store information. To manage Flash LSOs please visit 

<http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

This privacy notice covers the use of cookies by this site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.

This website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Tangient LLC. Please be aware that we, Tangient LLC, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy notices of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy notice applies only to information collected by this website.

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer want to use our service, you may correct, update, or delete it by making the change on our member preference page or by emailing us at 

or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. When you enter sensitive personally identifiable information such as login credentials on our login forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our website, you can email us at [help@wikispaces.com](mailto:help@wikispaces.org).

In the event Tangient LLC goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our website for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personally identifiable information.

We host a publicly accessible blog. If you wish to update or delete a comment posted to our blog containing personally identifiable information, you can contact us at help@wikispaces.com.

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our Web site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at help@wikispaces.com.

You can log in to our Web site using sign-in services such as an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personally identifiable information with us such as your email address to pre-populate our sign up form.

## Information Related to Data Collected for our Clients

Tangient LLC collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. We may transfer personally identifiable information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our Clients.

## Access to and Retention of Data Controlled by our Clients

Tangient LLC has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access to, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should contact Tangient LLC's Client (the data controller). If we are asked to remove data we will respond within 30 days.

We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Clients. Tangient LLC will retain this personally identifiable information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If we decide to change our privacy notice, we will post those changes to this privacy notice so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy notice at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy notice, please contact us at [help@wikispaces.com](mailto:help@wikispaces.org), on +1-415-863-8919, or at

Tangient LLC  
165 10th Street  
Suite 50  
San Francisco, CA 94103
